// creating an array and passing the number, questions and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "2 x 2 = ?",
        answer: "4",
        options: [
            "3",
            "4",
            "8",
            "2"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "4 ^ 3 = ?",
        answer: "64",
        options: [
            "12",
            "16",
            "64",
            "128"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "(16 + 8) x 2 = ?",
        answer: "48",
        options: [
            "48",
            "46",
            "44",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "1 x 1 = ?",
        answer: "1",
        options: [
            "2",
            "1.5",
            "0",
            "1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "90 - 62 + 14 = ?",
        answer: "42",
        options: [
            "47",
            "42",
            "45",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "77 / 11 = ?",
        answer: "7",
        options: [
            "7",
            "10",
            "6",
            "7.5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "2 x 2 x 3 / 3 = ?",
        answer: "4",
        options: [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "log5 ^ 25 = ?",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "1",
            "3",
            "5",
            "2"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "f(x) = x + 7 - 3 = 40 , x = ?",
        answer: "36",
        options: [
            "36",
            "46",
            "56",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "7 x 7 = ?",
        answer: "49",
        options: [
            "47",
            "49",
            "48",
            "46"
        ]
    }
]